This might seem like weird timing,
but I'm saying it now.
Wh-What?
I love you, Kiriyama Yui-san.
Please go out with me.
What are you doing?
I already turned you down.
But I still feel the same way about you,
and you might have changed your mind...
No! Never!
Not yet...
Not yet?
I've been wondering, why me?
Iori's a lot cuter than I am.
And Inaba's really pretty.
There's plenty to like about you.
But the biggest factor was intuition.
From the moment I first saw you,
I knew I would fall for you.
Then I fell in love with you,
and I still love you now.
So why are you telling me this now?
How do you feel about Taichi?
Taichi? Well...
I like him.
As a friend.
Wh-What about me?
I hate you as a friend.
No way!
You actually believed that?
I probably like you.
Ah, but only as a friend. As a friend.
But that's the best I
can manage right now.
Sorry, it's not you.
I'm not ready to go out with anyone.
Well, at least it sounds
like I have a chance.
Are you satisfied now?
Can we go back to the
classroom and have lunch?
Are you inviting me to join you?
No, my friends are waiting for me!
Ah, wait!
Just so you know, you're way behind
Taichi on my male friend list.
How did you know this
was going to happen?
What?! So Taichi is my biggest rival!
I switched with Yui yesterday and
happened to see the text from Aoki.
It was an accident.
And I figured it might
help give you two a jolt.
A jolt?
Well, it's up to you from here.
Bye.
We should get going.
I'm okay.
You're it, Taichi?
Yeah...
Are you Inaba?
Yeah, that's right.
Iori and I switched places.
So...
What did you think after seeing
Aoki and Yui during lunch?
What did I think?
It felt like I was watching
people from a different planet.
Why did you want us to watch them?
You can't seriously be so dense,
can you?
Huh?
Forget it.
I'll cut to the chase.
How do you feel about Iori?
Nothing is ever off-limits for you.
And it's more awkward when
you look like Nagase.
Perfect timing, right?
Why would you think that?
Well, I guess...
I really like our current relationship,
and I don't want to ruin that.
But...
Hey, it's just you two?
You're too early, Inaban.
Huh?
I really fooled you.
Iori!
Taichi, what did you do?!
Hell if I know!
Nagase was pretending to
have switched with you.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't get it either...
Because no matter what happens,
no matter how much you change,
I'll always be able to recognize
you for who you are.
Looks like you have some idea.
Yeah, I realized that I'm pathetic.
She wanted to trust me.
Want me to sock you good?
Yeah, go ahe—
Chase her down.
I'm not the one she needs.
Fujishima!
Yaegashi-kun...
Did you see Nagase?
Must we live in a world where a
couple is defined as a man and a woman?
What do you think?
I don't have time to talk
about that right now!
I'm looking for Nagase!
Move, Fujishi—
Nagase-san ran out the front gate!
I wasn't able to help her.
I'm guessing that you're
the one she needs.
Fujishima... Are you okay with that?
If you're the one Nagase-san
needs right now,
I won't stand in your way.
Hurry up now.
Nagase...
Where are you, Nagase?
Nagase!
Taichi...
I'm really sorry that I
didn't notice it was you!
After I made that promise...
What defines humans... defines us?
Nobody will notice a change on the inside
if you look the same on the outside.
Oh, I'm not blaming you
for anything, Taichi.
That was all my fault.
I'm sorry.
But you were trying to move on, right?
Thanks.
And now, it's my turn.
Uh, where to start...
I really admire you, Nagase.
You admire me?
I can't express myself the way you do.
I don't know how to show
joy, anger, or sorrow.
That's why I admire the
way you enjoy life.
That's because I keep switching roles.
You told me that the other day.
But is that really the case?
What do you mean?
What are you trying to say?
You seem to be confused.
When you joke around or play dumb,
get embarrassed or make dirty jokes,
do things spontaneously
or plan everything out,
think too much or don't think at all,
tell a joke before a
serious conversation
or act cold...
Um, what are you getting at?
In each case, you're still you.
What's that mean?
You're still Nagase Iori!
There's no such person!
One person can't wear
all of those masks!
That's normal.
Everyone wears a mask at some point.
I don't do it often.
You do it a lot.
That's all it means.
But I behave differently
around different people!
Lots of people will change
themselves to fit the situation.
But I'm always thinking about
which role I should play!
Nobody's strong enough to ignore
everyone else and be themselves.
But what I like changes
depending on the situation!
I couldn't even choose
a club for myself!
That just means you
like a lot of things.
And you're no worse than
the people who choose
a club because it looks easy.
That's pure sophistry.
Yeah, not at first though.
You know,
I admire you, Taichi.
You're always true to yourself.
No matter who I become,
you'll always be you.
I admire that stability you project.
Nagase...
I love you, Nagase Iori.
Will you go out with me?
Uh...
Hello.
It's been a while.
You can probably guess who I am.
Heartseed...
Yes...
I'll apologize up front.
Sorry.
But it's all you guys' fault
because you people are too boring.
Hey, what are you doing?
I already apologized.
Nagase!
Yes, thank you.
What'd Mr. Go say?
He's almost here.
And they managed to get
in touch with Iori's mom.
Hello there.
Bastard...
What is your objective?
Nagase Iori-san's body will die soon.
What are you talking about?!
You can play God with our lives?
Of course not.
But the fact remains that
I'm capable of many things.
Why should we believe you?
Well, it's up to you
to decide if you want
to believe me or not.
So, are you ready?
Listen carefully.
I want you to choose which personality
will die with Nagase-san's body.
Huh? Do you mean...?
For the next thirty minutes,
you'll be able to switch bodies
if you make an oral request.
There you have it.
Stop treating us like toys!
Taichi!
Understood?
You have thirty minutes.
He's telling us to choose who dies.
But we don't know that
Iori's going to die.
The doctors are doing their best.
Yeah, he could have been lying.
But he could have been
telling the truth.
Either way, we have to face reality.
Even if it makes you sick.
If...
If someone has to make the sacrifice,
I'll do it.
That's a load of bull.
You're volunteering to be the sacrifice?
Have you ever considered how it feels
to be on the other side?
You act like you're
concerned about others,
but you only care about yourself!
You're just a selfish freak!
Is that so wrong?!
That's right, I don't want to
see anyone else suffer!
It hurts me more than I can imagine
when I think about the
pain they must feel!
I can't stand it!
I'd rather suffer in their place!
At least then, I'd know how
much pain they endure.
That way, I could bear my own pain.
Right, I'm not doing
this for anyone else.
I'm a selfless freak for my own good.
Really...
Something's wrong with you.
Something's very wrong,
but it's a gentle form of insanity.
Gentle, awkward, and
stupid, seriously...
But you should understand our pain then.
I believe that Iori-chan
should be the one
who dies with her body.
How can you say that?!
I didn't want to say it,
but somebody had to.
Anyway, we need to tell
Iori-chan what's going on.
That's true.
Since I brought it up, I'll switch.
Please switch me, Aoki
Yoshifumi, with Nagase Iori.
Huh?
Why is everyone here?
I was talking with
Taichi by the river...
Iori, listen carefully.
You're...
In that case,
I have to die.
Nagase, it's not over yet.
I could never bring myself
to kill someone else and
take over their body.
I wouldn't be able to live with myself.
What about my mom?
She's supposed to be on her way here.
Oh...
Um...
Can I
talk with each of you
individually, one last time?
Taichi,
Iori wants to talk to you.
'Sup, Taichi.
Hey, Nagase.
Oh? You're the only one who
doesn't seem too different.
That's because I'm supposed
to be the stoic character.
Anyway, Taichi, thanks.
After talking to you,
my problems don't seem so significant.
I think I can learn to love myself.
You said that you love me.
I want to give a response now.
But you're probably expecting
a joke first, right?
Not really, but I figured
you might drop one on me.
Why are you the same as always?
Everyone else looked so sad.
I'm sad.
So sad, I could die.
But you must feel even worse.
If I cry, you won't be able to.
I don't want to die.
I want to keep on living.
I have so much to look forward to.
Why?
Why did this have to happen to me?
What did I do wrong?
Right after you told
me that you love me...
I love you, Taichi.
So I don't want you to go out with me.
Huh?
I mean, I'm going to die.
That wouldn't be much of a relationship.
How can you...
Instead, I want a memory
to remember you by.
So, let's kiss.
I'm sure that Inaban will forgive me.
Are you ready?
Who will it be?
Me.
Nagase Iori will die with
Nagase Iori's body.
Well, that would be the
logical conclusion.
Can I ask you a question?
I need an answer now.
You won't do this to anyone else, right?
Of course.
Oh, it's time.
Where's Iori?!
Wait...
Don't let this end...
Luck was on our side.
She's going to survive.
Huh?
It appears that there won't
be any permanent damage.
If you wait a little longer,
you'll be able to see her.
Ah, everyone. Good job.
Take this.
Consider it my apology.
It also serves as a get
well gift for Nagase-san.
You got us good.
Well, I knew it was a possibility.
So Iori's okay? She's alive?
That's wonderful.
Hey, how much of this was planned?
Well, I suppose you could say that
everything is part of my plan.
That's one way to look at it,
since you people don't seem to
realize what I'm capable of.
So you never intended to
do anything to Nagase?
I would never cause any trouble
for an innocent person.
I even made sure that her
cell phone didn't get wet.
I'm not going to ask
for your forgiveness,
but I hope that you won't hold a grudge
since you also benefited
from the experience.
Until next time.
Welcome back!
Thanks!
Sorry to make everyone worry.
Don't worry about that.
Anyway, did anything strange happen?
Nothing's happened.
There hasn't been any more body swapping.
Looks like it's all over then.
I hope you're right.
Anyway, let's dig in.
Aoki, make some tea.
Sure. Have a seat, Iori-chan.
Thanks. Sorry about this.
Come on! Taichi, Inaba, get to work!
Right.
I heard from Iori when
I went to visit her.
It sounds like you stole my first kiss?
That's going to cost you dearly.